Guide to the People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) Research Files
People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) Research Files
- Pest Control
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Deer—Contraception - 1 of 2 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Deer—Contraception - 2 of 2 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Deer—General/Miscellaneous (3”) - 1 of 12 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Deer—General/Miscellaneous (3”) - 2 of 12 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Deer—General/Miscellaneous (3”) - 3 of 12 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Deer—General/Miscellaneous (3”) - 4 of 12 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Deer—General/Miscellaneous (3”) - 5 of 12 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Deer—General/Miscellaneous (3”) - 6 of 12 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Deer—General/Miscellaneous (3”) - 7 of 12 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Deer—General/Miscellaneous (3”) - 8 of 12 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Deer—General/Miscellaneous (3”) - 9 of 12 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Deer—General/Miscellaneous (3”) -10 of 12 (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Deer—General/Miscellaneous (3”) -11 of 12 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Deer—General/Miscellaneous (3”) -12 of 12 (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Elk (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Moose (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Pigs (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - “Pest” Control—Type of Animals—Ungulates—Sheep (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - “Pest” Control—Types of Animal—Ungulates—Horses (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - “Pest” Control—Types of Animals—Ungulates—Goats (removal of goats from San Clemente island by the US Navy) (Box 156, Folder 18)
  - “Pest” Control—Ultra-sonic devices (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Confidential Subject Files, 11.5 linear feet
  - Addiction - 1 of 3 (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - Addiction - 2 of 3 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Addiction - 3 of 3 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - Aging (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Agricultural (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - AIDS—Miscellaneous evolving theory of the origin of the virus (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - AIDS—Types of Animals—Cats (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - AIDS—Types of Animals—General/Miscellaneous (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - AIDS—Types of Animals—Primates—General/Miscellaneous (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - AIDS—Types of Animals—Primates—General/Miscellaneous - Primates (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Balloon Releases (Balloons and the marine environment) (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Muscular Dystrophy (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Economics (cosmetics testing, cancer testing and the use of animals) (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Facilities—Advanced Tissue Sciences, Inc. (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Facilities—American Fund for Alternatives to Animal Research (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Facilities—American Type Culture Collection (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Facilities—BioSurface Technology, Inc. - missing folder (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Facilities—Clonetics Corp. (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Facilities—General/Miscellaneous (Fellowships for alternatives studies) (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Facilities—Health Designs, Inc. (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Facilities—Johns Hopkins Cener for Alternatives to Animal Research (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Facilities—Molecular Devices Corp. (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Facilities—National Testing Corp. (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Facilities—New Brunswick Scientific (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Facilities—Nonliving Systems Information Service (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Facilities—Organogenesis (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Facilities—Paracelsian (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Facilities—Stratagene Corp. (Scripps College, La Jolla, CA: monoclonal antibodies alternatives made from bacteria without the need for animal testing. (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Facilities—University of Saskatchewan (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Multiple Sclerosis (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Muscles (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Neurological - 1 of 7 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Neurological - 2 of 7 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Neurological - 3 of 7 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Neurological - 4 of 7 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Neurological - 5 of 7 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Neurological - 6 of 7 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Neurological - 6 of 7 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Neutritional - 1 of 7 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Neutritional - 2 of 7 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Neutritional - 3 of 7 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Neutritional - 4 of 7 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Neutritional - 5 of 7 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Neutritional - 6 of 7 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Neutritional - 7 of 7 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Obesity - 1 of 3 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Obesity - 2 of 3 (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Obesity - 3 of 3 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - Organ transplantation—Artificial Heart Information (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Organ transplantation—Cost/Who Pays? (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Organ transplantation—Criticism of Heart Transplants (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Organ transplantation—DeBakey, Bailey, Others (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Organ transplantation—Transplant Technology/Immunosuppression (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Organ transplantation—Xenografts/General - 1 of 4 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Organ transplantation—Xenografts/General - 2 of 4 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Organ transplantation—Xenografts/General - 3 of 4 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Organ transplantation—Xenografts/General - 4 of 4 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Osteopathy (mostly about Army experimentation with bone breakage using greyhounds as test objects) - 1 of 4 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Osteopathy (mostly about Army experimentation with bone breakage using greyhounds as test objects) - 2 of 4 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Osteopathy (mostly about Army experimentation with bone breakage using greyhounds as test objects) - 3 of 4 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Osteopathy (mostly about Army experimentation with bone breakage using greyhounds as test objects) - 4 of 4 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - OTA—Office of Technology Assessment—US Congress. (Correspondence, documents re: “Alternatives to Animal Use in Testing, Research, and Education.” - 1 of 2 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - OTA—Office of Technology Assessment—US Congress. (Correspondence, documents re: “Alternatives to Animal Use in Testing, Research, and Education.” - 2 of 2 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Pain 2” - 1 of 3 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Pain 2” - 2 of 3 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Pain 2” - 3 of 3 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Parkinson’s - 1 of 2 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Parkinson’s - 2 of 2 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Pneumonia (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Polio (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Pollution Hurting Wildlife—Plastic (plastic drink can holders) - 1 of 5 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Pollution Hurting Wildlife—Plastic (plastic drink can holders) - 2 of 5 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Pollution Hurting Wildlife—Plastic (plastic drink can holders) - 3 of 5 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Pollution Hurting Wildlife—Plastic (plastic drink can holders) - 4 of 5 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Pollution Hurting Wildlife—Plastic (plastic drink can holders) - 5 of 5 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Ponds (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Predator Control—Alligator (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Predator Control—Bear - 1 of 4 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Predator Control—Bear - 2 of 4 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Predator Control—Bear - 3 of 4 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Predator Control—Bear - 4 of 4 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Predator Control—Coyote - 1 of 3 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Predator Control—Coyote - 2 of 3 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Predator Control—Coyote - 3 of 3 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Predator Control—Feline - 1 of 2 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Predator Control—Feline - 2 of 2 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Predator Control—Fox (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Predator Control—Miscellaneous - 1 of 3 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Predator Control—Miscellaneous - 2 of 3 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Predator Control—Miscellaneous - 3 of 3 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Predator Control—Wolf (“Snowmobile Hunt claims hundreds of Wolves” Alberta and in the northern states)—1992-1995) 1” - 1 of 3 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Predator Control—Wolf (“Snowmobile Hunt claims hundreds of Wolves” Alberta and in the northern states)—1992-1995) 1” - 2 of 3 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Predator Control—Wolf (“Snowmobile Hunt claims hundreds of Wolves” Alberta and in the northern states)—1992-1995) 1” - 3 of 3 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Product Testing—Dermal Tests 2” - 1 of 2 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Product Testing—Dermal Tests 2” - 2 of 2 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Product Testing—Draize Eye-Irritancy Test 4” - 1 of 4 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Product Testing—Draize Eye-Irritancy Test 4” - 2 of 4 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Product Testing—Draize Eye-Irritancy Test 4” - 3 of 4 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Product Testing—Draize Eye-Irritancy Test 4” - 4 of 4 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Product Testing—General/Miscellaneous 4” - 1 of 8 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Product Testing—General/Miscellaneous 4” - 2 of 8 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Product Testing—General/Miscellaneous 4” - 3 of 8 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Product Testing—General/Miscellaneous 4” - 4 of 8 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Product Testing—General/Miscellaneous 4” - 5 of 8 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Product Testing—General/Miscellaneous 4” - 6 of 8 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Product Testing—General/Miscellaneous 4” - 7 of 8 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Product Testing—General/Miscellaneous 4” - 8 of 8 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Product Testing—Injuries - 1 of 2 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Product Testing—Injuries - 2 of 2 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Product Testing—LD50/Oral Tests (“Lethal Dose 50%” represents the single dose of a substance necessary to kill 40 percent of the animals used in an experiment in the laboratory.” From an article by Robert Sharpe, “The Death Test.” Distributed by the American Fund for Alternatives to Animal Research—AFAAR. Hearings on HR 1635 –“The Consumer Products Safe Testing Act”—concerning toxicity tests.) - 1 of 6 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Product Testing—LD50/Oral Tests (“Lethal Dose 50%” represents the single dose of a substance necessary to kill 40 percent of the animals used in an experiment in the laboratory.” From an article by Robert Sharpe, “The Death Test.” Distributed by the American Fund for Alternatives to Animal Research—AFAAR. Hearings on HR 1635 –“The Consumer Products Safe Testing Act”—concerning toxicity tests.) - 2 of 6 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Product Testing—LD50/Oral Tests (“Lethal Dose 50%” represents the single dose of a substance necessary to kill 40 percent of the animals used in an experiment in the laboratory.” From an article by Robert Sharpe, “The Death Test.” Distributed by the American Fund for Alternatives to Animal Research—AFAAR. Hearings on HR 1635 –“The Consumer Products Safe Testing Act”—concerning toxicity tests.) - 3 of 6 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Product Testing—LD50/Oral Tests (“Lethal Dose 50%” represents the single dose of a substance necessary to kill 40 percent of the animals used in an experiment in the laboratory.” From an article by Robert Sharpe, “The Death Test.” Distributed by the American Fund for Alternatives to Animal Research—AFAAR. Hearings on HR 1635 –“The Consumer Products Safe Testing Act”—concerning toxicity tests.) - 4 of 6 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Product Testing—LD50/Oral Tests (“Lethal Dose 50%” represents the single dose of a substance necessary to kill 40 percent of the animals used in an experiment in the laboratory.” From an article by Robert Sharpe, “The Death Test.” Distributed by the American Fund for Alternatives to Animal Research—AFAAR. Hearings on HR 1635 –“The Consumer Products Safe Testing Act”—concerning toxicity tests.) - 5 of 6 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Product Testing—LD50/Oral Tests (“Lethal Dose 50%” represents the single dose of a substance necessary to kill 40 percent of the animals used in an experiment in the laboratory.” From an article by Robert Sharpe, “The Death Test.” Distributed by the American Fund for Alternatives to Animal Research—AFAAR. Hearings on HR 1635 –“The Consumer Products Safe Testing Act”—concerning toxicity tests.) - 6 of 6 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Product Testing—Medical/Surgical (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Product Testing—Miscellaneous 2” - 1 of 4 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Product Testing—Miscellaneous 2” - 2 of 4 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Product Testing—Miscellaneous 2” - 3 of 4 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Product Testing—Miscellaneous 2” - 4 of 4 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Product Testing—Regulations/Labels - 1 of 3 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Product Testing—Regulations/Labels - 2 of 3 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Product Testing—Regulations/Labels - 3 of 3 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Psychology—Aggression/Dominance (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Psychology—Alternatives/Ethics - 1 of 2 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Psychology—Alternatives/Ethics - 2 of 2 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Psychology—General Miscellaneous (Ethical issues relating to painful experimentation on animals...sentient creatures have interests deserving of consideration. Alternative ethical approach is urged which would not permit painful experimentation on animals.) 3 ½” - 1 of 9 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Psychology—General Miscellaneous (Ethical issues relating to painful experimentation on animals...sentient creatures have interests deserving of consideration. Alternative ethical approach is urged which would not permit painful experimentation on animals.) 3 ½” - 2 of 9 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Psychology—General Miscellaneous (Ethical issues relating to painful experimentation on animals...sentient creatures have interests deserving of consideration. Alternative ethical approach is urged which would not permit painful experimentation on animals.) 3 ½” - 3 of 9 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Psychology—General Miscellaneous (Ethical issues relating to painful experimentation on animals...sentient creatures have interests deserving of consideration. Alternative ethical approach is urged which would not permit painful experimentation on animals.) 3 ½” - 4 of 9 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Psychology—General Miscellaneous (Ethical issues relating to painful experimentation on animals...sentient creatures have interests deserving of consideration. Alternative ethical approach is urged which would not permit painful experimentation on animals.) 3 ½” - 5 of 9 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Psychology—General Miscellaneous (Ethical issues relating to painful experimentation on animals...sentient creatures have interests deserving of consideration. Alternative ethical approach is urged which would not permit painful experimentation on animals.) 3 ½” - 6 of 9 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Psychology—General Miscellaneous (Ethical issues relating to painful experimentation on animals...sentient creatures have interests deserving of consideration. Alternative ethical approach is urged which would not permit painful experimentation on animals.) 3 ½” - 7 of 9 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Psychology—General Miscellaneous (Ethical issues relating to painful experimentation on animals...sentient creatures have interests deserving of consideration. Alternative ethical approach is urged which would not permit painful experimentation on animals.) 3 ½” - 8 of 9 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Psychology—General Miscellaneous (Ethical issues relating to painful experimentation on animals...sentient creatures have interests deserving of consideration. Alternative ethical approach is urged which would not permit painful experimentation on animals.) 3 ½” - 9 of 9 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Psychology—Isolation (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Psychology—Learned Helplessness (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Psychology—Stress - 1 of 2 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Psychology—Stress - 2 of 2 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Racing (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Radiation (“Radioactive” Animals loose or buried in campus in New York; stories of the use of animals in radiation experiments, even the use of stillborn babies.) - 1 of 4 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Radiation (“Radioactive” Animals loose or buried in campus in New York; stories of the use of animals in radiation experiments, even the use of stillborn babies.) - 2 of 4 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Radiation (“Radioactive” Animals loose or buried in campus in New York; stories of the use of animals in radiation experiments, even the use of stillborn babies.) - 3 of 4 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Radiation (“Radioactive” Animals loose or buried in campus in New York; stories of the use of animals in radiation experiments, even the use of stillborn babies.) - 4 of 4 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Reproductive/Sexual 4” - 1 of 11 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Reproductive/Sexual 4” - 2 of 11 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Reproductive/Sexual 4” - 3 of 11 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Reproductive/Sexual 4” - 4 of 11 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Reproductive/Sexual 4” - 5 of 11 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Reproductive/Sexual 4” - 6 of 11 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Reproductive/Sexual 4” - 7 of 11 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Reproductive/Sexual 4” - 8 of 11 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Reproductive/Sexual 4” - 9 of 11 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Reproductive/Sexual 4” - 10 of 11 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Reproductive/Sexual 4” - 11 of 11 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Reptiles—Turtles (sea turtles, tortoises, loggerhead, etc., and the struggle with survival in a beach environment. (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Rescue (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Rodents—General/Misc - 1 of 3 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Rodents—General/Misc - 2 of 3 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Rodents—General/Misc - 3 of 3 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Rodents—Guinea Pigs (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Rodents—Hamsters (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Rodents—Mice—1987 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Rodents—Mice—1988 - 1 of 2 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Rodents—Mice—1988 - 2 of 2 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Rodents—Mice—1989 - 1 of 3 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Rodents—Mice—1989 - 2 of 3 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Rodents—Mice—1989 - 3 of 3 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Rodents—Mice—1990 - 1 of 2 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Rodents—Mice—1990 - 2 of 2 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Rodents—Mice—1991 - 1 of 2 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Rodents—Mice—1991 - 2 of 2 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Rodents—Mice—1992 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Rodents—Mice—1993 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Rodents—Mice—1994 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Rodents—Mice—1995 - 1 of 2 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Rodents—Mice—1995 - 2 of 2 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Rodents—Mice—1996 - 1 of 2 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Rodents—Mice—1996 - 2 of 2 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Rodents—Mice—1997 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Rodents—Mice—2000 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Rodents—Mice—Pre-1987 or no date (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Rodents—Rats-Pre-1980 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Rodents—Rats—1980-1982 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Rodents—Rats—1983 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Rodents—Rats—1984 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Rodents—Rats—1985 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Rodents—Rats—1986 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Rodents—Rats—1987 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Rodents—Rats—1988 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Rodents—Rats—1989 - 1 of 2 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Rodents—Rats—1989 - 2 of 2 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Rodents—Rats—1990 - 1 of 2 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Rodents—Rats—1990 - 2 of 2 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Rodents—Rats—1991 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Rodents—Rats—1992 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Rodents—Rats—1993 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Rodents—Rats—1994 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Rodents—Rats—1995 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Rodents—Rats—1996 - 1 of 2 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Rodents—Rats—1996 - 2 of 2 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Rodents—Rats—1997 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Rodents—Rats—1998 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Rodents—Rats—1999 (empty) (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Rodents—Rats—2000 (empty) (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Rodents—Rats—No Date (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Rodents—Woodchucks (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Severed Heads - 1 of 2 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Severed Heads - 2 of 2 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Sheep and Goats - 1 of 2 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Sheep and Goats - 2 of 2 (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - Shock (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - Skin (Box 127, Folder 17)
  - Sleep (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Smuggling/Poaching Birds (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Smuggling/Poaching Reptiles (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Space 2” - 1 of 6 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Space 2” - 2 of 6 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Space 2” - 3 of 6 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Space 2” - 4 of 6 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Space 2” - 5 of 6 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Space 2” - 6 of 6 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Spinal Injury - 1 of 6 (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Spinal Injury - 2 of 6 (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Spinal Injury - 3 of 6 (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - Spinal Injury - 4 of 6 (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - Spinal Injury - 5 of 6 (Box 128.1, Folder 1)
  - Spinal Injury - 6 of 6 (Box 128.1, Folder 2)
  - Sports Medicine - 1 of 2 (Box 128.1, Folder 3)
  - Sports Medicine - 2 of 2 (Box 128.1, Folder 4)
  - Stroke (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Surgery - 1 of 2 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Surgery - 2 of 2 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Teratogenicity (birth defects, drugs that cause one reaction in animals and another in man) - 1 of 2 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Teratogenicity (birth defects, drugs that cause one reaction in animals and another in man) - 2 of 2 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Toxicity Testing—Automotive Fuel (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Toxicity Testing—Environmental Pollutants - 1 of 4 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Toxicity Testing—Environmental Pollutants - 2 of 4 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Toxicity Testing—Environmental Pollutants - 3 of 4 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Toxicity Testing—Environmental Pollutants - 4 of 4 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Toxicity Testing—Food and Drink - 1 of 2 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Toxicity Testing—Food and Drink - 2 of 2 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Toxicity Testing—General/Miscellaneous - 1 of 8 (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Toxicity Testing—General/Miscellaneous - 2 of 8 (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Toxicity Testing—General/Miscellaneous - 3 of 8 (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Toxicity Testing—General/Miscellaneous - 4 of 8 (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - Toxicity Testing—General/Miscellaneous - 5 of 8 (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - Toxicity Testing—General/Miscellaneous - 6 of 8 (Box 129, Folder 18)
  - Toxicity Testing—General/Miscellaneous - 7 of 8 (Box 129, Folder 19)
  - Toxicity Testing—General/Miscellaneous - 8 of 8 (Box 129, Folder 20)
  - Toxicity Testing—Industrial Chemicals - 1 of 2 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Toxicity Testing—Industrial Chemicals - 2 of 2 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Toxicity Testing—Medical Application (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Toxicity Testing—Military Application (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Toxicity Testing—Pesticides - 1 of 4 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Toxicity Testing—Pesticides - 2 of 4 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Toxicity Testing—Pesticides - 3 of 4 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Toxicity Testing—Pesticides - 4 of 4 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Transplants--Liver (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Transplants—Brain (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Transplants—General/Miscellaneous—Negative (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Transplants—Heart—Negative - 1 of 2 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Transplants—Heart—Negative - 2 of 2 (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - Transplants—Heart—Positive - 1 of 4 (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - Transplants—Heart—Positive - 2 of 4 (Box 130, Folder 15)
  - Transplants—Heart—Positive - 3 of 4 (Box 130, Folder 16)
  - Transplants—Heart—Positive - 4 of 4 (Box 130, Folder 17)
  - Transplants—Kidney (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Transplants—Pancreas (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Transplants—Tissue (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Transportation—Animal (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Tuberculosis (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Turtle Physiology—Alternative materials (Computer programs for dissection of animals) - 1 of 2 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Turtle Physiology—Alternative materials (Computer programs for dissection of animals) - 2 o 2 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Turtles—Correspondence (Box 131, Folder 7)